V-What?
You're Kidding!
Hey!
Be careful, Bonareff.
Even a small wound can end up like this.
Why are you still alive?
Such a stubborn man.
What Idget would get himself
killed by his own stance?
A little scratch is all it takes
for my stand to get inside of you.
Then my stan will creep
under your skin and kill you.
How are you going to get out of this one?
Run!
Oh, what the hell?
This is a toilet!
I'm always finding myself being
attacked in places like toilets!
Shit, what a dirty bowl.
Oh.
They're searching for me.
It's just a matter of
time before they find me.
All right, then. I'll fight.
Ready when you are.
I'll slice you to pieces.
What happened?
Why aren't they attacking?
Why don't you do something?
Damn it!
What a sucker.
Laugh!
Oh, sick!
Jaya!
Is this it?
Her stand?
How the mighty have fallen, Polnareff.
Now, let's see what you can do for me.
Why don't you start with that dirty
toilet bowl By licking it clean.
Love!
Excuse me, but I'm looking for a
French guy named Jean-Pierre Polnareff.
Have you seen him around here?
Have you?
Ah, Mr. Polnareff.
Mr.
Polnareff has stepped
away to the restroom.
Restroom, huh?
Yes.
The restroom is through that door,
down the hall, and on your right.
The restroom is through
this door and to the right?
Yes.
It's Jotaro. Not good.
Don't come in here.
Please don't come in here.
It's a trap!
By the way, how do you know Polnareff?
Ah,
earlier he came to my
rescue when a drunkard
was having trouble keeping his
hands to himself, Mr. Chotaro.
I see.
Let me ask you one more thing.
Just now you called me Jotaro,
but how do you know my name?
Mr.
Polnareff told me.
That can't be.
I told everyone not to mention my name.
Naturally, that includes Polnareff, too.
Well, the killer of my dearest son, J.
Kyle, was to be disposed of first.
But I suppose that can wait.
Your son.
Die!
What?
Let's go, let's go.
Yeah!
No!
Well, now I get it.
Aren't you just a little bit worried?
I suppose you haven't
had much time to think
about your companions while you're here.
Kakyoin, it's me.
I can't seem to find Jotaro anywhere.
Do you know where he is?
Just a minute.
I'm getting the door right now.
Jostar, son.
The enemy!
Oh, sorry, everyone.
It's nothing.
Huh?
Who in the world are
these people? Justice!
He's the one who was on the street.
It can't be!
Are they... dead?
Hang on!
Let's go!
Outside!
I'll catch up with you.
Madam, please, hurry.
Thank you very much, young man.
What's going on?
It's that woman, Enya.
She's the stand user in this town.
She controls this fog.
And even the slightest wound
will allow her to control you.
Just like them, as a matter of fact.
I'm already affected, mom.
I don't know when she'll
seize control of me.
She forced me to lick the
Toilet bowl, that bitch.
I'll get her for this.
In any case, we have to find
that woman as soon as possible.
But with all this madness going on, the
town is now filled with dead people.
What now?
Here's the big entrance.
Beep!
Mhm!
Pull her out!
Old splash!
Shit!
Oh, my God.
We've been waiting for you, our dog.
My apologies for being late.
Looks like you've fully
recovered from your injuries.
Holnarev, I will have to explain later.
That thing is invincible.
We need to hit the main body,
or this will go on forever.
Enya must be watching
from somewhere inside that
hotel and laughing her
head up at us right now.
Avdol, could I bother you for a light?
After all the light.
Well, you certainly haven't aged
very gracefully since I saw you last,
have you, Enya?
Enya?
It can't be!
Are you saying this old
lady is a stand user?
Hey!
Enya is a beautiful young woman,
not some old hag like her!
But you know that too, don't you?
Thanks to our past battles,
I noticed a characteristic
that's shared by all stand users.
When a stand user inhales even a
small amount of cigarette smoke,
there's a vein in their
nose that surfaces.
You're kidding, right, Jochiro?
Yeah, I'm lying.
But we found the sucker, didn't we?
Enya's left hand, it was always hidden.
Your son also had a right hand
in place of his left hand.
If you really are that
woman in disguise and J.
Giles' mother, then...
Hmm.
Your left is...
Your right.
Jotaro!
Run, Jotaro!
Get out of here now!
She'll put a hole in your leg.
When that happens, you're finished!
If you don't watch your step
even for a spits second,
you'll end up at the feet of your enemy.
Jotaro.
What a pain.
I'm not letting you toy
with Polnareff anymore.
Listen up.
Before you take one more breath, I'll put
an end to that stand, once and for all.
What?
Why, you son-murdering, good-for-nothing,
pretentious piece of crap scumbag.
What's that?
What the...
Star Platinum is inhaling Justice's head?
Oh, Polnareff.
I'm so sorry, everyone.
Just because I was careless,
I dragged all of you down.
Damn that woman!
Come to think of it, I should have known
that something was wrong with her, right?
Like, hiding her left hand like that.
Who would have thought that old
hag was in disguise and was...
Hey, Avdol!
How can you be alive?
Weren't you shot in the
head by whole horse?
Yes, my friend.
I did get shot right here in
the center of my forehead.
But Jaegyle stabbed me from
behind, just as it happened,
and the counterforce of his
blade pulled me backwards.
so the bullet did not mortally wound me.
I'm so glad,
Avdol,
that you're alive.
You're alive.
Yes.
What should we do with the old woman?
I have a million questions about
Dio that I want to ask her.
So when did you start to
suspect this old woman, Jotaro?
From the first moment I
laid eyes on the old woman.
From the very beginning?
Oh, yeah.
She was just way too normal to be
hanging out with those weirdos.
By the way, just how did you
find out where we were, Avdol?
Oh, I got the phone call from Mr.
Joestar this morning telling me. A call?
Ah, back then.
Huh?
Hey, wait!
But, but then, but, but then
that would mean that Mr.
Joestar knew that you were
alive this whole time.
Ha, ha, ha.
Well, as a matter of fact, in
India, I was tended to by Mr.
Joestar and Jotaro.
Huh?
You guys already knew back in
India that Avdol was alive,
but you didn't tell me about it?
Polnareff,
you have a bit of a
loose tongue Yeah If you
foolishly blurted it out I
thought Avdol-san wouldn't
be able to recover from
his injuries in peace
So I made the suggestion
to keep it quiet What?
Oh, oh, shit So I was the
only one left out. Damn!
Huh?
Mmm.
Lord, Dio.
Old woman.
A bud of flesh. Old
woman,
the true nature of Dio's stand?
Please, tell us what it is.
Tell me, you've been betrayed by Dio.
Speak!
He's not the kind of man you think he is
Please!
As once.
Huh?
I will tell you.
Try asking Lord Deals instead.
Oh, shit!
Dio never allows anyone
into his heart. Never.
It is disappearing.
The city itself was a stand.
Well, I guess that takes
care of the burial.
She was a formidable enemy.
Hey!
Isn't that whole horse lying
over there in the dirt?
He's still breathing.
Leave him alone.
He needs to be hospitalized.
He's no longer a threat.
Holly...
Let's go!
After crossing this desert,
we'll finally be in Egypt.
Deal.
Let's go.
Thank you.